Most of the gurus online teaching about
how to grow your business
and make loads of
money made all of their money from
teaching you how to make loads of
money in their business,
not from actually running the business.
It's always been strange to me,
and I've always found that quite funny.
How can someone that never really had a
big fitness business teach you everything
there is about having a big fitness
business?
The other thing is,
a lot of these people drive fancy cars.
And I know, I'm guilty of it too,
but the majority of people don't tell you
that
that car is on finance. So is mine.
If I'm completely honest, my fitness
business never gave me loads of money
where I could pay off people's mortgages
or
walk into a Lamborghini and buy a car.
But what it did was give me a life of
freedom. I no longer had a boss.
I could work online.
And these have been the only things
that I've needed to run my
businesses for the last seven years:
good Wi-Fi connection, laptop,
mobile phone,
and some type of professional audio.
So just be weary online when people say,
"I can help you make 10K a month," when
they only made 10K a month by selling to
people that they can make 10K a month.
And here's the elephant in the room as
well.
A lot of people rent stuff to make it seem
like they're wealthier than they really
are. Like this.
Don't be fooled too easily because this
isn't even my house. [chuckles]